《黑镜》
《1500万价值》
放荡辣妹莱斯·宝贝的最新进展
New from Wraith Babes, the hottest girls in nasty situations.
"折磨达人"就要开始了!
Let's play Botherguts!
加入我们吧
Come on!
三  二  一!
Three, two, one!
开始!
Go!
帮她去除游泳圈
Chuck her a bun!
不饿么?  这仅仅是个开始!
Not hungry?! That's a first?!
加油!
Come on!
他们应该会疼吧!
That'd hurt!
太有意思了!
Brilliant!
真他妈的有意思!
Fucking brilliant, that!
你等下  这个机器经常这样  稍等
That one does that sometimes. Hang on.
这附近有个地方变形凸出了
There's a little knob in here somewhere.
应该是这里唯一真实存在的东西
Almost the only real thing in there,
连这都是从培养皿里长出来的
and even that's grown in a Petri dish.
谢了
Thank you.
上帝啊
For Christ's sake!
肥猪  你来的真是时候!  也不照照自己
Way to mood-kill, blubbernaut! Cheers for the reflection!
上一分钟我还仙仙欲坠  接下来就看到你这个猪脸
One minute I'm in slitsville, the next there's a haunted pig
还不如直接了断我得了
gawping at me. They may as well have cut to a war crime!
你漏东西了
You missed a bit.
死肥猪
Pie ape!
你也看到了吧?
You see that?
死肥猪一个
Fucking pie ape!
过不了多久  他也会穿上那身柠檬装
He'll be in lemon and all before long!
塞尔玛·特斯拉
Selma Telse.
霍华德·曼德布洛特
Howie Mandelbrot.
玩具兵人
Toy soldiers.
关于他们的内容充斥在你每天信息的头版
Each headlines their own content on one of your eight daylight streams.
他们也像你一样  从这里开始
But they started here, like you.
他们用辛勤的过去换来了光辉的现在
Putting their back into giving back for a brighter now.
他们像你一样为了实现一举成名的梦想
Each paying their dues like you,
付出了自己的努力
hoping to become a hot shot.
这不能用"好"来形容
That wasnt good...
而是"无可挑剔"!
that was beyond incredible!
你来决定获胜者  你来决定他们的命运
You decide the victors, you control their fates,
在达人秀一切都有你做主
you make the call on Hot Shots.
放荡辣妹莱斯·宝贝的最新进展
New from Wraith Babes, the hottest girls in the nastiest situations.
让我们开始欣赏吧
So let's view it.
等待重放
Resume viewing.
这里带给你全方面的视觉体验
You are going to see it all.
只在莱斯·宝贝
Exclusively on Wraith Babes XL.
你还想用那只手干别的吗?
Hey, what else were you planning to do with that hand?
快舔我下面  宝贝儿
You lick my pussy, baby.
我让你欲火焚身
I turn you on!
你好  我是罗克西
Hi, I'm Roxy, hello.
好  我是艾薇
Hi, I'm Evie.
他被禁止进入这里了
Didn't let him sign in.
让他去下面的22楼报道
Told him to report to 22 down.
早就说过
Told ya!
那个懒货要穿柠檬装了
He's gone lemon, the lazy fuck!
你觉得这个咋样?
What do you think?
有点夸张
It's a bit much.
也是
Yeah.
新生活中最好的事情?  该从何说起呢?
Best thing about my new lifestyle? Where do I start?
可以自己选择衣服  还有我很喜欢黄金
I love choosing my own clothes and I love gold.
我觉得那能展现出最真实的自我
I feel like it really expresses who I really am
我还喜欢往窗外看看
and I love looking over outside.
外面的景色很美  真心希望你们都能看到
It's so beautiful sometimes, I just wish that everyone could see it.
新衣服不错
Nice outfit.
挺适合你的
Suits you.
怎么说  有时候  诚实是很残忍的
Well, honesty is ruthless so I suppose it's just honesty...
但这的确是个事实
ruthless honesty.
吹干手着呢
Drying my hands.
不错
Impressive.
好好享受...
Have fun...
我是说  在那个...
I mean, on the...
普通用户  你好
Hey, regular user!
放荡辣妹莱斯·宝贝的最新进展
New from Wraith Babes, the hottest girls in the nastiest situation.
请选择观看...
Select view...
笨死了
Dick.
[第一部分结束]
[第二部分]
不好意思  这个算是残屑
Detritus. Sorry.
不会吧
Come on!
等下  这个需要点小技巧
Wait, wait. There's a knack to it.
- 小心手指  - 没事  放心吧
- You'll take your fingers off. -  Trust me.
办法真好
Smart.
宾·曼森
Bing Manson.
你可以叫我宾厄姆
Short for Bingham.
艾比·卡纳
Abi Carner.
你可以叫艾比·卡纳
Short for Abi Carner.
新来的吧  我没有见过你
You're a new person. I've not seen you.
上周我还在21楼
I just went 21 last week.
本来计划去雅列顿  我妹妹在那里
I wanted to go to Airdale My sister's there, but...
很明显那里人满了
It's full, apparently.
水果不错  还是值得冒险的
Proper fruit. It was worth the risk.
是这里最天然的东西
The most natural thing in there's probably
说不定都是从培养皿里弄出来的
grown in a Petri dish.
可不是
Yeah.
不过  还是挺好吃的
Quite good, though.
在这里  就是这个样子
Yeah. That's the right way round.
如果你买一个便宜的  你还是要把里程骑回来
When you get the cheap one, you end up having to pedal it off.
不一会儿你就需要更多糖分
Then you want more sugar.
然后你又要再把里程追回来
Then you're playing catch-up and I've...
我就经历过  恶性循环
I've been there. It's a vicious circle.
你为什么不试试CPT程序?
Cant you just use that CPT app?
那是什么程序?
What's that?
是个认知行为类的软件
This cognitive behavioural thing.
它会告诉你选择合适的事物
It realigns your thinking to pick healthy food.
在你熟睡的时候慢慢向你灌输
Whispers you into it while you sleep.
听起来不错  我该试试
Yeah, I should try that, yeah.
我很喜欢你那天唱的歌
I liked your singing the other day.
那个时候唱歌就不会有人听到我在尿尿
I was trying to sing so no-one could hear me pee.
我又不是塞尔玛那样的人
I'm not Selma or anything.
你的嗓音真的很不错
You've got a phenomenal voice.
那是我听过最美妙的歌...
It was the most beautiful song...
你...  是不是觉得我有点笨手笨脚的?
Y... You think I'm being cheesy?
我的确有点蹩脚
All right, I am being cheesy.
但你唱的真的很好...
But it was beautiful, so, you know...
现实有时候并没有那么精致
Reality's cheesy sometimes. Not often,
你不得不承认...
admittedly, but...
比如说现在
Now.
就是...
Yeah...
谢谢你这么说
Well, thank you.
只不过是随便一哼吧
It's just noises, though.
有节奏的随便一哼
Noises in the right order.
别谦虚了  你唱的真的很不错
Dont downplay... you're good.
那歌倒是不错  很多年前的了
The song's good. It's old.
我妈妈以前经常唱  她是从她妈妈那里学来的
My mum used to sing it and she learnt it from her mum.
然后我也从妈妈那里学来的
A hand-me-down.
你没有想过去达人秀试试?
You thought of trying out for Hot Shot?
我么?
Me?
- 为什么不?  - 在评委面前唱歌?
- Why not? -  Singing in front of Judge Hope?
还是杀了我吧
I'd die! Seriously,
下辈子能去合唱团都算不错了
I'd be halfway to the afterlife come the chorus.
你比那优秀
No, you'd walk it.
首先  我不会去
A, I wouldnt.
再说我也没有那么多的里程
And B... I dont have that clockage.
光入场券都要一千二百万的里程吧?
It's, what, 12 mil just to enter?
那样骑多长时间?  不吃不喝六个月?
What kind of bike time is that? Six months?
- 是那么多  但...  - 我现在仅仅够糊口
- Yeah, but... -  I'm hand to mouth.
我知道他们为了上那个舞台省吃俭用
I know people save and stuff to get onto that stage
塞尔玛就是这样做的  但是你知道么?
and then there's what Selma did. But, you know what?
我是不会那样...
I'd rather not give myself...
我知道  所以我会送你入场券的
Yeah, but I'll gift it to you.
全部一千二百万  我都会给你
The full 12, I'll gift it.
别开玩笑了
Dont be ridiculous!
我是认真的  我富余着
Seriously, I've got it spare.
你能多出来一千二百万?
You've got 12 mil spare?
我哥哥留给我的
My brother left it me.
他是开电视台的?
Own a channel, does he?
不  不是...
No, he...
他去世了
He died.
他去年去世了...
He... He died last year,
然后这些里程都转移给了我
so it got transferred to me.
刚好比六个月的里程多  我保留了下来
Just over six months' worth, but I've kept it.
那你为什么不自己使用呢?
Why dont you spend it on you, then?
买什么?  买那么多鞋给谁穿?
And buy what? Some new shoes for my doppel to wear?
那就升级一下你的MOS...
I dont know, upgrade your MOS...
或者吃个半死?
Or get a Fat Attack season pass?
那就买个服务墙吧
Buy one of those wall buddies.
那种关闭后可以陪你聊天帮你解决问题的新款
The new ones that talk to you after shutting and solve your problems.
他们就想神一样引导你的梦境
They guide your dreams, like gurus.
他们能做的真的很神奇
It's amazing, really, what they can do.
再加一个镜子进来?  然后让我看起来多么可怜?
A mirror plug-in? That shows me how I look as a werewolf?
这还能干什么?
What's the point?
- 的确有点可怜  - 那些只是东西  它们...
- I know it can be quite funny. -  It's all just stuff. It's...
那只是东西  只是一些花俏的东西...
It's stuff, it's confetti, it's...
你的歌声才是真是存在的
You've got something real.
还有比这更好的去处么?
What better to spend it on?
你也只是在厕所听到我唱歌
You heard me singing in a toilet.
你觉得那很真实?
Is that real?
比这一年中发生的所有事情都真实
More than anything that's happened all year.
我不能接受那样贵重的礼物
I cant take that kind of clockage off someone.
那可是一千两百万
It's 12 mils, no way.
是我自愿的
Let me do this.
你看看周围...
I... I look around here, I just...
我只是希望有什么真实的事情发生
I just want something real to happen.
哪怕只有一次
Just once.
我会弄砸的
I'd mess up.
你不会的  再说我也不介意
You wouldnt. I dont care anyway.
我会陪你一起去  我会要求你去的
I'll go with you. I'll be able to force you.
我会强迫你去的
I'll force you to go.
就是明天了
It's tomorrow.
好么?
Come on!
快说行
Say yes.
那我只好说"好"了
I'll go as far as to say, "OK."
那也可以接受
Which proves acceptable.
太感谢了
Thank God for that.
我要走了...
Walking away now.
小傻瓜
You loon!
这个也可以接受
I can live with it!
我当然愿意浪费了那一切
I'd love to fucking ruin that and all.
什么?
What?
要一千五百万?
15?
开什么玩笑...
A flippin' joke...
放荡辣妹
New from Wraith Babes.
莱斯·宝贝的最新进展
The hottest girls in the nastiest situations.
就这样!
Yeah!
[第二部分结束]
[第三部分]
不敢相信我真的要这么做了
Cant believe I'm doing this.
我要去参赛了
I am doing this.
我做不了这个
I cant be doing this.
你能把那退回去么?
Can you trade it back?
你说入场券?
The ticket?
别开玩笑了
Dont be mad.
那给人很大的压力
It's a lot of pressure to put someone under, you know.
我没有不感激的意思  只是...
Dont think I'm not grateful. But it's, it's just...
你在自言自语...
You're babbling.
对  我是在自言自语
I'm babbling.
我给你做的这个
I made you this.
这个从来没有在你手上超过一天
You never get to keep them more than a day,
所以我又做了一个
but there it is, anyway.
这次叠的很平整
It folds flat.
你就可以把他放到腰带里了
So you can keep them in your waistband.
谢谢
Thank you.
这...  你知道
It's, you know...
只是普通的东西
something.
请看大屏幕
Face the screen, please.
他是你的朋友还是家人
Is he your Friends And Family allocation?
请把手伸过来
Hand, please.
这不是永久的  对吗?
That's not permanent, is it?
没错  最多保持两个月
No. Two months max.
向右走  然后通过安检
Round to the right, and through the scanner.
我们现在去哪?
Where do we go now?
在这等着
You wait here.
等多长时间
How long?
那么我们做什么呢?
So, what do we do?
不知道
I dont know.
- 嘿 嘿 嘿  - 滚开
- Hey, hey, hey. - Fuck off.
是那个黑发女孩吗?
Her with the dark hair?
对  对  对  漂亮的那个
Yeah, yeah, yeah. The pretty one.
好的  让一下
Yup. OK. Move.
他们让你去面试
They want to preview you.
- 什么?  - 面试  快点
- What? -  Preview. Come on.
- 他和我是一起的  - 手
- He's with me. -  Hand?
给我看看你的手
Show me your hand.
好吧  你也过来
OK. You, too.
那不公平  她是新来的  那不公平
That's not fair. She's new. That's not fair.
顺序不是我决定的
I dont pick the order.
我已经在这等了整整一周  而她刚进来
I've waited here all week, and she's just walked in.
每个人都有面试的机会  顺序不是我决定的
Everyone will get seen eventually. I dont pick the order.
但我是个好歌手
But I'm a good singer.
我能唱  我唱的很好  我的确唱得很好
I can sing. I'm a good singer, I am.
- 一边去  - 这不公平
- Stand aside. -  It's not fair!
不公平
It's not fair!
- 往那边点  - 站到那
- Next lot. -  Stand there.
你愿意未来的某天像塞尔玛一样红吗?
Would you like to be as big as Salma one day?
是的  我是说
Yeah, I mean...
你能对着屏幕
Could you say that
用一个完整的句子表达这个意思吗?
as a self-contained sentence into that screen?
我愿意未来像塞尔玛一样出名
I guess I'd like to be as big as Salma one day.
好的  到舞台那边吧
OK. Proceed to stage area.
完事了吗?
Are we done?
- 一起表演吗?  - 只是她
- Both performing? -  Just her.
- 好吧  表演什么?  - 唱歌
- Okay... and what are you? -  Singer.
- 要点吗?  - 不  谢谢
- Compliance? -  No, thanks.
是的  谢谢  每个参赛者是必须喝的
A-ha. Yes, thanks! It's compulsory for all contestants.
更重要的是  它可以防止你过于紧张而呕吐
More to the point, it'll stop you puking with nerves.
- 她要去表演  - 那么...
- She's got to perform. -  Well...
看  只喝一小口  没事的
Look, just sip it, you'll be fine.
只是有点泡沫  一会儿就过去了
Just a touch of light foam. It'll pass.
好好利用它
Make the most of it.
别的地方可没有这种东西
You cant get this stuff anywhere else.
- 你还好吧?  - 是的
- You OK? - Yeah.
没事吧?
You OK?
是的  只是
Yeah. Just...
不太清楚  看东西有点模糊  没事
I dont know. Things are just wider apart. I'm fine.
- 你确定?  - 是的 我很好
- Really? -  Yeah, I'm fine.
好了  该你上场了
Right. You're on.
请过来点
A little closer, please.
再过来点
Little closer.
站到灯光下  亲爱的
Into the light, love.
- 我们看到的这位尊姓大名?  - 艾比·卡纳
- And who're we looking at here? -  Abi Khan.
你今天准备什么才艺  艾比?
What are you going to do for us today, Abi?
唱歌
I'm going to sing.
亲爱的  说话大声点
You speak up, love.
我们不咬人
We dont bite.
我要唱歌
I'm going to sing.
你愿意为我脱了上衣吗
Hey, would you mind lifting up your top for me?
能脱掉上衣吗?
Can you take off your top?
我想看看你的双乳
I want to check out those titties.
来吧
Come on. Mucho feranto.
不让看?
No titties?
她说她到这是来唱歌的
She says she's here to sing.
然而我是来看美胸的
I got to see those titties, though.
好吧  美女
Come on, girl.
我是说  该死!
I mean, damn!
你很辣
You hot.
请唱吧
Please, just sing for us.
好吧  我打断一下
OK. I'm going to stop you there.
这
That was...
毫无疑问
without a doubt...
可能是我们在这一季听到的最好的歌声
probably the best piece of singing we've had this season.
是的  做的很好
Yes! Well done!
精彩的演出
Fair play.
但是我不得不说
But I have to say...
不  不  我不得不说
No. No, no, no. I have to say,
事实上
actually,
我同意雷夫的观点
I'm with Rafe on this one.
尽管你的声音很动听  声音确实也不错
Good though your voice is... and it is good.
但它不是世界上最有吸引力的声音
It's not the most magical sound in the world.
只是很动听
It's just... good.
我认为不是所有人都认为你的声音很动听
I dont think anyone's really hearing it.
观众并不只有男士们
Certainly not the guys in the audience.
这看起来将成为你今后发展的障碍
These looks you got going on kind of get in the way.
男士们喜欢你  可女士们要恨你了
Men will want you. Women will hate you.
从你登上舞台
All the time you're on stage.
就情不自禁的幻想你
Couldnt help picturing you.
在情色场景中的样子
In an erotic scenario.
如果我没说错  很有挑逗性
Getting pretty turned on, if I'm honest.
没错
Right.
你有种纯纯的美
You've got this pure beauty
很迷人
What seems to be a knockout figure.
而且这极具吸引力的单纯正在延续
And this sort of interesting innocence going on.
我想这种东西在雷夫的色情频道
That's something I think Rafe's erotica channels
可以得到充分的展示
could really play with.
没错  这就是我看你第一眼
Absolutely. That's what I thought
你给我留下的印象
the moment I saw you.
就在那一刻
The moment.
我看出来了
I'd watch.
我不知道哪位在这的男士不这样认为
I dont know a man here who wouldnt.
说实话  一些我们女士也是这么认为的
To be honest, some of us girls might join you.
放开我!
Get off me!
别答应他!  艾比!
Dont! Abi!
别答应!  艾比!  艾比!
No! Abi! Abi!
我认为...
I dont think that's quite...
你永远都不用再去骑车了  一分钟都不用
You will never have to pedal again. Not one minute.
我们真的可以合作
We could really work with you.
去年  我们有歌手  歌手  歌手
Last year we had singers, singers, singers.
很多的歌手
So many singers.
想要成为一位歌手你必须是独一无二的
So, to be a singer you have to be truly exceptional
水平一般的人在歌坛是没有容身之地的
There's just no slots left for an above average singer.
至少在今后的几年没有位置  查丽蒂  你说呢
Not for the next few years, at least. Charity?
没错  歌手已经饱和了
No. Saturation point, singer-wise.
听着  我们说  从头开始
Listen. We said, right from the start.
我们将进行些与这一季不同的内容
We'll go with something different this season.
这就是他为什么在这!
That's why he's on the panel!
她将在我们的潮流中成为巨星
She would be a star on our stream.
一颗巨星
A star.
在他那...
On his...
你最多只能当个花瓶
You're furniture, at best.
抛开那些羞耻感
Forget about all the shame, and all that ppht-ppht-tew.
我们一起克服它
We medicate against that.
你将永远快乐
You will have pleasure forever.
现实点吧  甜心  选择改变
Realistically, sweetheart, it is that,
或是回去继续骑车
or the bike.
我  我不这么认为...
I, I dont think...
你有点让我生气了
This is starting to annoy me.
你认为谁在为这聚光灯供电
Who do you think is powering that spotlight?
是成千上万的观众  是他们
Millions of people. That's who.
全部  在这之外  就在此刻
All of them, out there, right now.
在脚踏车上度过他们实实在在的一天
Putting in an honest day on the bike,
当你站在镁光灯下  他们还在发电
while you stand in the light they're generating
徘徊
and dither.
你知道吗?
You know what?
观众给予了一切  做你现在该做的事
They would give anything. Do anything to be where you are now.
我说得对吗?
Am I right?!
你想反对  尽管那什么也不是
You want to cock a snook at all that, as though it's nothing.
尽管他们什么也不是
As though they're nothing.
那使我感到恶心
And that makes me sick.
但是  你知道
But, you know what?
或许你天生就是蹬车的命
Maybe you do belong on the bike.
因为你看起来不太愿意离开那里
Because you dont seem to be very willing to step off it.
我想离开
I do want to.
那你决定了吗
We have a decision?
做吧!
Do it!
我做
I suppose.
- 继续!  - 棒极了!
- Go on! -  Well done!
[第四部分]
新生活中最美好的事情...
Best thing about my new lifestyle...
我要接触到很多帅哥
I get to meet lots of hot guys.
莱斯对我很好
Wraith treats me well.
你又来了!
For Christ's sake!
这可是要花钱的!
I pay for this!
要花钱的!
I... pay... for... this!
我累死累活的就是为了这  你...  滚开
I pump my arse off, and you... Fuck you!
就那样  往前爬  猪头
Yeah, keep waddling, pig tits.
小心点别他妈的走错了
Find your horizon and fuck off over it!
这就是我的梦想
It's a dream.
我就要
I get to live...
生活在
in a...
一个美丽的地方
beautiful place.
然后
And...
穿着...
wear lots of...
漂亮的衣服
beautiful things.
简直是在做梦
It's a dream.
资金不足
Insufficient funds.
来自莱斯·宝贝...
From Wraith Babes...
"加油  姑娘..."
C'mon, girl...
莱斯·宝贝特别企划
a Wraith Babes reality special.
有一天我会像塞尔玛一样有名
I guess I'd like to be as big as Thelma one day.
上百万的观众见证了她在达人秀
Millions watched her glide through the Hot Shot curtain of dreams
大展歌喉的一幕
to sing her heart out.
接下来发生的震惊了世界
What happened next shocked them all.
我们会合作的很好
We could really work with you.
你做出决定了么?
Do we have a decision?
现在  请观赏她的首次情色表演...
Now, watch her stunning erotic debut...
不  不  不  不  不要...
No, no, no, no, no...
我们这次的嘉宾是?
So, who do we have here?
我是阿比
I'm Abby.
你之前上过达人秀节目
You were at Hot Shot.
那时真令人印象深刻
You were real impressive.
等待重放
Resume viewing!
- 不  我不看  - 等待重放
- No! No! -  Resume viewing!
等待重放
Resume viewing!
看看你
Look at you.
靓丽动人
All clean and shiny.
广告时间禁止出入
Portal disabled during commercial.
你会看到你想看的一切
You'll see everything.
这里带给你全方面的视觉体验
You'll see it all!
张开嘴
Open your mouth.
再大点  吞下去...
Open... take it in...
享受它  对  就这样...
take it in... yeah...
不  不要...
No! No! No! No!
[第五部分]
借个道  麻烦你
Could you stand aside, please?
跟我到后面来  请站我面前
Come up into the back, in front of me, please.
你在开玩笑么?
Are you messin'?
哪个?
A what-nic one?
少数种族的
An eth-nic one!
看到了
On it.
你一会儿预演  跟我到后面来
We're going to preview, all right? Want to follow me in the back?
你让人恶心
You're a prick!
下一个
Next, lot.
站在那!
Stand there!
你是干什么的  魔术师?
So what are you, a magician?
表演的
An entertainer.
请对着镜头用一句话介绍下自己
Could you say that down the screen as a self-contained sentence?
我是个表演者
I'm an entertainer.
上台前  你需要喝这个
Before you go on, you need to drink a compliance.
- 后台已经给我了  - 是么  好吧
- They give me one back there. - Really? OK.
那样的话  你就可以...
Well, in that case, you are good to...
上台了
go.
你是谁?
Who are you?
宾·曼森...
Bing Madsen.
你为我们准备了什么?
What are you planning to do for us?
搞什么?!
What the fuck?!
一种表演
A sort of performance.
一种表演?
A sort of performance?
是的
Yes.
还是个有秘密的男人!
Man of mystery!
那我们开始吧
I suppose we'd better see it.
好的
OK.
头太大
Knob'ead!
跟龟头一样
Fucking cock!
别过来  我会动手的
Stop or I'll do it. This is a main artery.
你要过来一步  我就死给你看
Keep walking, you kill me.
等我说完了  你们想干什么就干什么
No-one stops me till I've said my piece. Then you can do what you like.
哥们  你死了算了
Man, just fucking kill yourself.
别威胁我  不然我发誓  老子会把你揍活过来
Get heavy on me, I swear to God, I kick your ass back to life,
然后再砍掉你的死人头
just so I could cut your goddamn head off.
有意思了
Go on!
我觉得我们应该听听他想说什么
I think we should let him speak.
说!
Speak!
听听他要说什么
Let's hear what he has to say.
开始吧
Well?
说吧
Come on.
我们在听  如你所愿
Got our attention, as requested.
你想说什么?
What do you want to say?
你准备做一个演讲  是么?
Have you prepared a speech, is that it?
快说啊!
Speak!
我没准备演讲  没准备任何东西  想都没想...
I havent got a speech. I didnt plan words. I didnt even try to...
我只知道我得来  站在这  我要你们听到
I just knew I had to get here, to stand here, and I wanted you to listen.
真正地听到  不是像你们之前那样
To really listen, not just pull a face like you're listening,
假装在听
like you do the rest of the time.
你们脸上的是真实的感情  而不是假装出来的
A face that you're feeling instead of processing.
你自己强忍着一张脸
You pull a face, and poke it towards the stage,
还指着台上说我们装模作样
and we lah-di-dah, we sing and dance and tumble around.
在你们眼里  我们不是人
And all you see up here, it's not people,
是供你发挥的素材
you dont see people up here, it's all fodder.
素材越不真实  你们也越起劲
And the faker the fodder, the more you love it,
因为假的东西才是你们真正在乎的
because fake fodder's the only thing that works any more.
它虽是我们生活中需要容忍的  但不是全部
It's all that we can stomach. Actually, not quite all.
我们还能感受到  切身的痛和真真正正的恶意
Real pain, real viciousness, that, we can take.
对  往一个胖人嘴里塞满东西
Yeah, stick a fat man up a pole.
我们可以开怀大笑  因为我们有这个权利
We laugh ourselves feral, because we've earned the right,
我们都在运动  而他还松弛浮肿
we've done cell time and he's slacking, the scum,
所以我们有权利笑他
so ha-ha-ha at him!
我们之所以这样无趣
Because we're so out of our minds with desperation,
是因为我们不知道还能做些什么
we dont know any better.
我们能接触到的就是你们这些素材  我们只能选择你们
All we know is fake fodder and buying shit.
我们彼此谈论的
That's how we speak to each other,
我们能干的  也就是购买你们这些垃圾
how we express ourselves, is buying shit.
什么  我的梦想?
What, I have a dream?
我们最大的梦想就是给自己的开心网
The peak of our dreams is a new app
再购买一个根本不真实存在的程序?
for our Dopple, it doesnt exist!
一个无法触摸到的东西?  !
It's not even there!
我们梦寐以求的东西竟然都不存在
We buy shit that's not even there.
你给不了我们真实美丽存在的东西
Show us something real and free and beautiful. You couldnt.
对吧?  那会摧毁我们的
Yeah? It'd break us.
我们对那已经失去了感觉
We're too numb for it.
我甚至都可能窒息
I might as well choke.
我们能承受的也只有那些新奇
It's only so much wonder we can bear.
无论你找到多少新奇  你也只肯放出一小部分
When you find any wonder whatsoever, you dole it out in meagre portions.
那部分还是你精心挑选
Only then until it's augmented, packaged, and
精心包装过的
pumped through 10,000 preassigned filters
等到上台时  他早已平庸至极
till it's nothing more than a meaningless series of lights,
我们累死累活的骑车  是要去哪里?
while we ride day in day out, going where?
掌控什么?
Powering what?
我们能控制的也只有那些小房间小屏幕
All tiny cells and tiny screens and bigger cells
或者大房间大屏幕这样的事情!  草!
and bigger screens and fuck you!
草他妈的  归根结底  我们也只能干这些
Fuck you, that's what it boils down to.
你他妈的只需要坐在那里就可以  随意左右人的命运
Fuck you for sitting there and slowly making things worse.
去你的聚光灯  去你的伪善
Fuck you and your spotlight and your sanctimonious faces.
你们都他妈的认为我跟你们一样
Fuck you all for thinking the one thing
从没有想过任何真实的事情
I came close to never meant anything.
你们尽情的起哄  尽情的嘲弄
For oozing around it and crushing it into a bone, into a joke.
这只不过给王国多增加了一个笑柄
One more ugly joke in a kingdom of millions.
操这里的一切
Fuck you for happening.
我痛恨你  我  我们每一个人
Fuck you for me, for us, for everyone.
都下地狱去吧
Fuck you!
刚才那个  毋庸置疑
That was, without a doubt,
我在这个舞台上见过的最真实的事情
the most heartfelt thing I've seen on this stage
开播以来都没有发生过!
since Hotshot began!
好啊!
Brilliant!
你...
You...
你表达的很清晰
you're so articulating something we all,
我是指大厅里的每一个人
and I mean everyone in this hall,
我们一致认定
something we all agree on.
尽管我们也许没完全理解
Even though we may not comprehend all of it.
但我还是可以说我们都感受到了
I think I'm right in saying we do feel it.
尤其我自己
Even me.
作为这个人物  你的确征服了我
I know you've got me down as this creature.
的确如此...
You know, hey...
我知道你的背景
I get where you're coming from.
- 我喜欢你的表演  - 这不是表演
- I like your stuff. -  It's not stuff.
是事实  对吧?
It's truth. Am I right?
你的事实  毋庸置疑  是真实的
Your truth, admittedly, but truth nonetheless.
你是对的
And you're right.
真实是可遇而不可求的
Authenticity is in woefully short supply.
我愿意听你再次演说
I'd like to hear you talk again.
怎样可能?
How so?
我的电视台可以给你提供这样一个位置
The slot on one of my streams
在那里你就可以尽情的演说了
where you can talk just like that.
我一定会看  激情澎湃!
I'd watch it. It was such great passion.
他是对的  你在那会火的  伙计
He's a'right. You're a little hot there, bud.
自杀这招你玩的太漂亮了
That throat cutting thing? Neat gimmick.
你觉得如何?
What do you say?
30分钟时长  每周两次?
30 minutes twice a week?
接受
Do it!
兔崽子  快同意啊
Go on, you bastard.
接受
Do it!
不用再骑车了
Beats the bike.
谁说不是
Certainly does.
我们请到奥利弗  奥利弗会一直的吃
We have with us Oliver. Oliver ate and ate
吃够17块为止  他今天来挑战了!
till he hit 17 stone and he's here today to try and beat us
就在"折磨达人"!
on Botherguts!
继续吃啊
Keep going.
我不得不打断你  简直无法忍受
OK, I'm going to stop you there. That was achingly terrible.
你平庸的跟毛巾一样
You have the magnetism of a towel.
我都不愿意再看到你
I dont ever want to look at you again.
我得承认  我很抱歉  宝贝
I have to agree. I'm so sorry, love.
你点都不讨人喜欢
You came across as fundamentally unlikeable
而且还一无是处
and really quite worthless.
可不是?
Right?
就算你下面留着蜜  我也不会操你
You could fill that pussy with honey and I still wouldnt fuck it.
我是个好歌手  我能唱  真的
I'm a good singer. I can sing, yeah.
我注定要当个歌手
Cos this is my destiny
我能唱  操!
and I can sing, fu...!
就这样  是么  哈利?
Like that, dont you, Harry?
是么?
Say it.
喜欢
Yeah.
光上周就推出了
15,000 new wardrobe options
15000个新功能
launched last week alone.
它们会在你房间里帮你高效的消耗掉
It effectively translates as 15,000 new ways to kill time
你来生前的所有时间
in your cell before you explore an afterlife
如果你还有来生的话
which doesnt exist anyway.
你觉得你有可能会想这些悲哀的事情么?
With any luck, it'll take your mind off those saddle sores?
你知道我为什么还没有动手么?
You know the only thing stopping me from slashing myself open right now?
我可能不会立即死去
I might not die right away.
在我死之前  他们会
And before I went, they'd find a way
向我那抽搐的身体收
to charge my twitching half-dead cadaver,
20000里程洗净墙壁
20,000 merits for swabbing the walls clean.
- 可不是  - 总之
- Yeah. -  Anyway,
如果你要死的话
hang on in there
就死在那里面吧
if you must.
他们说  我们是一起的
We're all in this together they say.
可不是  好吧
Yeah, right.
永别了
Farewell for ever.
下周同一时间再见
Till the same time next week.
直播结束
Stream off-line.